https://www.linkedin.com/in/ksingh94/



Kulpreet Singh Front End UI/UX Software Developer

Professional Business Manager with more than four years of experience in business marketing, management and development of new business interests. Now Continuing with Front End Web Development and Coding.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Hotel Management

Westwood Investments Inc.

Guthrie, OK

08/2016 - Current

- Managing Employees
- Resolving reservation complications
- Clerical Duties
- Attaining new guests/clients
- Hotel ambassador working with nearby event organizers to create business through mutual gain.
- Review customer feedback to assess ways we can better the quest stay experience.

Co-Owner/Manager

ProExtreme Carwash Moore & Noble, OK 07/2015 - 07/2018

- Maintaining mechanical equipment with proper maintenance.
- Promoting and advertising car wash specials to get more business.
- Depositing money and ensuring all machines were stocked/filled and working.

EDUCATION

B.A. in Psychology with Sociology Minor The University of Oklahoma

08/2012 - 12/2016

Full Stack Coding Certification Southern Methodist University

03/2020 - 09/2020

LANGUAGES

English					
Spanish				0	
Punjabi		0	0	0	
Hindi		0	0	0	

SKILLS



ORGANIZATIONS

AmeriCorps

08/2011- 05/2012

- Mentor to Kindergarten students
- Teacher's aide for 5 Second-Grade Teachers

OUIS

Oklahoma Undergraduate Indian Society August 08/2012 - 12/2016

- Freshman Representative
 - August 2012 May 2013
- Treasurer
 - August 2013 May 2014

AASA

Asian American Student Association 08/2012 - 12/2016

- Freshman Representative
 - August 2012 May 2013

University of Oklahoma Big Event Volunteer 08/2012 - 12/2016

Community Service

CERT

Crisis Emergency Response Team 08/2016-12/2016

> Student Emergency Response Team Member

REFERENCE

Kuljit Singh

Americas Best Value Inn 2323 Territorial Trail Guthrie, OK 73044 (580) 504-1445 kcmicro@yahoo.com